<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<metadata>
  <identifier>Attack.of.the.Killer.Refrigerator.1990.VHSRip.DivX-HeYWooD.avi</identifier>
  <scanner>Internet Archive Python library 0.8.1</scanner>
  <publicdate>2015-12-06 01:18:13</publicdate>
  <title>Attack of the Killer Refridgerator (Attack of the Killer Refrigerator) 1990.VHSRip.DivX-HeYWooD.avi (1984)</title>
  <mediatype>data</mediatype>
  <collection>opensource</collection>
  <uploader>worldpeacehaven@gmail.com</uploader>
  <addeddate>2015-12-06 01:18:13</addeddate>
  <curation>[curator]validator@archive.org[/curator][date]20151206012225[/date][comment]checked for malware[/comment]</curation>
  <fail-reasons>JPEGThumb:filetype doesn't match name:attack-screenies.jpg
JPEGThumb:filetype doesn't match name:attack.jpg</fail-reasons>
  <creator>Media House Productions; dir. by Michael Savino</creator>
  <description>A 1984 short film. Released on VHS in 1990. This is a rip by HeYWooD, apparently from 2007 or earlier (see the "Web info" file for more information). This file was apparently released on ed2k, and was retrieved from Uloz.to. It wasn't very easy to find.

This copy is missing the accompanying material (behind-the-scenes video and another film called "The Hook of Woodland Heights"). There aren't complete or high quality scans of the VHS packaging either. The large poster image and the Web info aren't part of the HeYWooD release.

These files may or may not be what they're supposed to be, and may or may not be in good condition with respect to conformance with the original VHS tape. Oh well. :( I hope that a better copy comes to light for preservation for the future, since I quite enjoyed this little film.

Uloz.to link that this was retrieved from (beware of possible malware): http://www.ulozto.net/xZVcenPv/attack-of-the-killer-refrigerator-1990-vhsrip-divx-heywood-avi

ed2k link (beware of possible malware): ed2k://|file|Attack.of.the.Killer.Refrigerator.1990.VHSRip.DivX-HeYWooD.avi|138100736|B6752CAA68BFC97F1653DC8E85A2D213|h=AXJMWGQSTN53T3NC6GMFC56PDTULRGGC|/</description>
  <date>1984</date>
  <year>1984</year>
  <subject>Attack of the Killer Refridgerator, Attack of the Killer Refrigerator, 1990, VHSRip, DivX, HeYWooD, avi, 1984, ed2k, movies, films, video, short movies,</subject>
  <rights>Apparently abandonware.</rights>
  <publisher>Media House Productions</publisher>
  <language>English</language>
</metadata>
