<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<metadata>
  <identifier>RushWar2ResourcesWildsqukvrKr7f7Q</identifier>
  <collection>opensource_movies</collection>
  <description>Play RushWar Now - http://goo.gl/j7AK4m&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;RushWar is a City Building Game with a little twist, can you win the war?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are six kinds of resources in Rushwar: Crops, Lumber, Stone, Iron, Silver and Population. The first four are construction resources and are each collected by attacking wilds that exist on the map. Silver are primarily collected through taxation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Small amount of resources can be generated from the cities production establishments, like Quarry, Sawmill, Farm and Iron mine but they generate only small amount of resources and players will need to attack wild to gain more resources to produce armies and upgrade buildings quickly&lt;br /&gt;As stated above, Wild exists to provide resources in the game, you attack them with "maraud" to gather resources and "seize" to gather resources and increase your city's production. Each type of wild has an associated resource (and resource production boost) that it will give.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Players can also seize wilds to give production boost to resource generation in their citys resource production centers. Each city is limited in the number of wilds it can have seized -- it can't own any more than its City Halls level, and it cannot own more than 10 wilds (of any type). When a wild is seized, its level determines the production boost -- level 1 wild (the easiest level) gives a 3% boost to production, whereas a level 10 wild (the hardest level) would give a 30% boost; every level increases the boost given by 3%.&lt;br /&gt;If the wild seize limit is reached and players try to seize wilds still, the attack will automatically fail to seize the wild.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Music by Machinimasound.com / Cloister Of Redemption&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We have license to all the games under www.lekool.com</description>
  <mediatype>movies</mediatype>
  <scanner>Internet Archive Python library 0.8.1</scanner>
  <subject>UCd5QJdnKc0yof6pFqYtj9aw</subject>
  <title>RushWar - #2 Resources &amp; Wilds</title>
  <subject>Youtube rip by ET3RN4L</subject>
  <subject>RushWar</subject>
  <subject>#2</subject>
  <subject>Resources</subject>
  <subject>&amp;</subject>
  <subject>Wilds</subject>
  <subject>qukvrKr7f7Q</subject>
  <publicdate>2015-04-29 01:19:44</publicdate>
  <uploader>worldpeacehaven@gmail.com</uploader>
  <addeddate>2015-04-29 01:19:44</addeddate>
  <curation>[curator]validator@archive.org[/curator][date]20150429012610[/date][comment]checked for malware[/comment]</curation>
</metadata>
